Translated by Releska
The sky in the dark is so dark
If that's not true, and your dream was so beautiful
It's a time when the sun rises like this
It's a time when the wind blows
I'd like you and I
If I love you, I'd be able to see you
Because I do not want to be a bad person
I don't feel good.
It's a joke.
If you experiment with the machine, it's a lot of things.
We were all in a different world than the universe.
I don't even know where it is.
I don't even know what's going on in the world.
But I'm not in a hurry.
It's the first time I've ever had a child, and I feel so happy to be with Muka Muka together!
Muka Muka is here!
I'll be back in the middle!
Muka Muka has been preparing for today now!
We don't have a high standard!!
We've got a high standard now!
We can go now!
Mr. Azato is on the other side!
Mr. Azato is here!
Mr. Azato!
I was happy to have a child today!
Muka Muka, let's go~!
You guys can see the stunning place!
Thank you!
Muka Muka, let's go!
I heard you were looking forward to seeing Muka Muka home in this special place!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Oh, wait a minute!
I'm here.
Huh? Don't you like it?
Huh?
What did you do to the old man?
This is my private beach.
Why do you have such a place in the morning?
We're in the rain.
There's a lot of effort to get there.
This is a luxury beach.
The Jumbo Nooses and the Kiyai.
Whoa! What's wrong with you?
I can't do it.
Wait, where did you get it from?
I don't know who it is.
You don't even have time to experience it.
Let's go.
This is pretty good.
Huh?
There's something wrong with your eyes.
I said it.
What?
Don't do it!
What are you doing in such a place?
I'm the one who's the best.
I'm the second one.
Well, let's have fun.
The sea is wide.
Hey, Yuna.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with me?
It's the sea.
No, it's the sea.
I want to be the one who's the best.
I'm the one who's the best.
It's you.
We should stop this from going.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
That island is so full of the people who can only get one year!
They are so full of people who can only get one year!
Well, you know, there's a lot of people looking for that island.
It's not like you can't get rid of those people.
I see, Ranca-san is a lot of people.
There's a lot of people going!
What? I'm just joking!
I see, me?
Ranca-san, let's see what you can do if you get a source from the bathroom.
Let's get rid of this!
I'm glad that I can get rid of those people.
I'm glad that I can get rid of those people who can only get rid of those people.
That's what I'm talking about, isn't it?
But I'd like to try it out.
It's not fair! It's not fair!
That's right! Stop it!
Ah! It's my ball!
It's my ball! It's my ball!
It's not a ball! It's my ball! It's my ball!
That's my ball!
Stop it! Stop it!
It's my ball!
Oh, no!
You're almost there, huh?
It might be a good ball.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Where did I go?
Huh, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's going on with you like that?
I can't get out of here.
Oh!
Die!
What's going on?
Hey! Let's do it!
I'll give you a hug today!
What is it?
I don't care!
I don't even notice!
I'm not interested!
Don't be interested!
What...
What?
Sorry, I'm bringing you dinner!
I'm fine, I'm fine!
I'm fine!
Did you know I didn't see any bad luck earlier?
I shouldn't have done that before!
Let's go!
Hippie, isn't it too bad?
What is this place?
I don't know much, but it's quite complicated.
This is the most complicated battlefield.
Ah! I was thinking about it!
I did it! I did it!
Where could I hear this voice?
Down there!
Is it in the back?
What?
Where is that?
Is it a mountain?
What's wrong with you?
Kiyoto!
Wait a minute!
It's too dark here.
I don't want to see you again.
I want to see you again.
I didn't see you.
What's wrong?
Did you say you were coming?
That's right.
I didn't feel good.
I was worried about you.
That's right.
You've been running for the past few days.
The past few days?
That's right.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not worried about you.
Hype!
I want to see you again.
It's not like that.
I see.
I don't want to see you again.
No, I'm not really.
I'm not really sure if I'll be the last one.
I'm not sure if I'll be the last one.
I'm looking for you.
Oh, you're right.
Let's go.
I'm not going to be the last one.
Can I put it on?
What's this game?
Ren!
Where are you, Seita?
Which place was this?
Seita, this is...
Game Cent!
I see!
The game we watched him play until the eyes!
If you had defeat him before, he would've taken all his eyes!
Should we just make him win?
I was going to do it!
Hey, hey!
Yorosuke!
I told you to run over here, right?
It's a cliff.
It's way too far.
I've got a way to the right.
I like it.
Huh?
I like it!
Where?
I like it.
I don't know if I can hear you.
I can't hear you.
I'm sorry I quit.
I'm not like that.
I see.
This is dangerous.
I can't hear it.
I'm dangerous.
I can't hear you.
Will I be able to escape?
I'm done! I'm done!
I'm done!
I'm in the 5th grade!
How are you?
Wait a minute!
What's going on?
If Kagami returned to the hospital,
what's next?
Alright, I'll open the door and see what's in there!
I'm going to die!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
I'm in the 5th grade!
I was going to die!
I like to be angry, but I'm pretty happy with this!
I'm in the 5th grade!
I'm sorry!
I won't let you go!
What's going on?
I'm in the 7th grade!
Mom! Help me!
Oh, it's here!
This is it!
Hey, hey, hey!
Mom! This is my neighbor's neighbor!
I'm coming from here!
Let's go together!
I have to find a way to get to the fast ones.
Oh, that's so scary!
Mom, wait.
Mom, wait!
We have to wait!
If I win this game, I won't be able to run away.
Huh? Wasn't it here?
I won this game?
I won this game!
I did it!
Ah! I knew it!
Everyone was hiding in there.
That's a lot of trouble.
We have to get over the line.
So I have to go to this game.
I don't know if it's possible.
I'm going to run away!
I'll take care of you.
Oh!
That's right.
I thought I'd be able to sleep.
I'll...
Everyone, wait!
It's too late, so...
I have to go back to my normal life.
I like it.
Sentai, I got used to it.
Huh?
Wow!
Come with me!
Ahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha!
Huh?
Are you okay?
Did you lie down?
Huh?
I'm so scared!
Uh...
It's...
Sendai!
Alright.
I'm going...
Ui-ba!
I love you!
I told you it was a lie.
This is just a joke.
I'm scared, so I'm scared.
That's why I'm here.
There are too many of them.
Let's go home quickly.
No, no!
Muka Muka!
I heard a voice from Muka Muka.
It's eight o'clock!
Muka Muka!
It's six o'clock!
There's a lot of them.
I love you, Ui-ba!
Huh?
Muka Muka!
I'm scared, Ui-ba!
Muka Muka! Muka Muka!
Muka Muka!
I was in the room of the door.
It's not the time to eat, is it?
I found it!
Let's do it, I found it!
It's five o'clock.
I forgot it.
I'll open it.
Wow!
I found it!
What are you doing?
It's hard to do it.
I couldn't do it if I put it in the box.
I did it!
I found it!
If I put it in the box, I can't talk to you.
I want to talk to you.
Huh?
I found it!
What's wrong with you?
What was that?
I found it,注意 your health.
I found it!
I got it!
Ah, thank you very much, Mr. Hamukamu-chan, for helping me.
Ah, my beach ball.
Look.
Hey, is this a treasure?
No, it's not.
There's a lot of treasure here.
I have to give it to you.
Ah, it's not here yet?
I think there's something wonderful about it today.
Ah, I've killed it.
I'm going to die.
I've been waiting for the letter.
No, I'm not going to die.
I almost died.
Let's meet again soon.
Ah,ikkudachi, please tell me something.
I said that.
This is dangerous!
Let's go, Shiro!
Over there!
Good job!
That's it!
Yay, baby!
I got it!
Yay! I got it!
Good job!
Amazing!
Thank you!
It's a cute baby.
I'll do anything for you!
That's why I'm not going there.
You can't do anything!
You have a treasure!
It's not that!
That's why!
That's right!
That's right, it's not bad at all.
Yeah, that's why there's something to eat.
It's like a roll.
Huh?
What's the name of the island's treasure?
It's called the Yuzhou treasure called the Yuzhou treasure.
What's that?
That's the one.
It's the Yuzhou treasure.
That's right.
It's a good thing to do a roll.
I mean,
the Yuzhou treasure is a treasure that you can collect.
It's a treasure that you can collect even if you eat it.
How do you do it?
You should clean yourself up once yourera are gone.
Nothing's been done wrong,
I just cut it,
but it's not something you can does in half time.
I couldn't say it though.
What's up?
What do you mean?
What do you mean, what do you mean what do you mean?
To start this show,
it was onto Yuzhou State's Gae Kut bye!
Me?
He died so late!
He did something are in this game!
That's why he ran away.
I think he was stable so far.
It was great.
I was so happy to be with Gai Kutsu-san.
I was so happy to be with you alone.
Oh, you don't believe me, do you?
Oh, that's not what I meant.
I was really happy.
Do you want to see me?
Well, I was really happy to be with you.
Huh?
We don't need to worry about anything.
I'm really happy.
I was really happy to be with you.
Oh, that's not what I meant.
Translated by Releska
It's so sad, it's so sad!
I wonder why I was so tired until now...
It's the first time I've ever been able to meet Yukiyara!
This isn't a big deal!
If you're here, I'd like to collect all the Shima Joos, and collect all of them!
Next time, Muka Muka Paradais!
Stay tuned for the next episode of Muka Muka!
The next episode of Muka Muka!